My name is Chinatsu Kano.
Thanks for having me.
[all] Welcome to the Inomata household!
I have a little something.
[Taiki's mom] Gosh,
you didn't have to do that.
She's really beautiful, isn't she?
Looks just like
your grandmother did, Taiki.
Isn't this nice, son?
She really livens up the place.
[Taiki] That's a major understatement.
I'm already losing it just from
seeing Chinatsu in regular clothes.
There she is. On our stairs.
In our kitchen with my mom.
She's even eating sushi!
How am I going to make it through this?
[opening theme song playing]
BLUE BOX
[Taiki] So this is my life
for the next two years?
EPISODE 2
YOU HAVE TO GO TO NATIONALS
This won't end until she graduates?
[cheering]
I was pumped the other day
just for advancing to the second round.
But living under the same roof?
It's like competing in the Olympics.
[knocking at door]
[Chinatsu] Taiki.
[funky music playing]
Um, your mom told me to tell you
that the bath is free.
[exclaims]
[Taiki] Loungewear?
And straight out of the bath,
she's glowing even more than usual.
I'll go when I'm done reading this!
[gasps] Oh, my gosh, no way.
That isn't this week's Jump, is it?
[Taiki] What the--
[Chinatsu] I've been running around
so much with the move,
I haven't gotten
to read this week's latest one.
[Taiki] So close!
Why don't I lend you my copy!
- Really?
- Yeah, of course!
If she comes any closer, I'm in trouble.
Huh?
What's going on?
Hm. I'm just relieved.
It's been nerve wracking
living in another person's home.
Our parents may be good friends,
but I've only met yours a couple times.
So having a familiar face around
from morning practice like you,
you letting me borrow your manga...
I feel more at home.
[Taiki] More at home?
All right, goodnight.
[Taiki's psyche] Feelings of guilt...
[Taiki] At the end of the day,
I'm still just a guy.
[unzipping]
Is she not even fazed
by the thought of living with...
a guy her age?
[exclaiming]
[exclaims]
Because if she isn't,
then I'm being an idiot for no reason.
[yells]
[quirky music playing]
Let's go!
[Kyo] Where did all this
upbeat energy come from?
Aren't you supposed to be moping around?
I'm allowed to be happy
when things are good.
Look, I understand that you're hyped,
but make sure people don't find out
you're living together.
- What?
- [Kyo] Don't "what" me. Look over there.
She's so awesome.
Not there, guys.
Get the camera to zoom out.
[exclaims]
[Kyo] I tried to tell you already,
Chinatsu is super popular.
And if any of those guys found out...
[boy] Don't move now, basketball hoop.
[Taiki grunts]
[quirky music ends]
Regardless, consider yourself lucky.
Even though your parents decided,
you get to live with someone you like.
So you might end up dating after all.
[Taiki] No way, dude.
She chose to stay behind
in Japan on her own.
She's so dead-set on sports,
throwing in a, "Hey, wanna go out?" now...
not an option.
So after thinking about it,
I want to go
to nationals this summer, too.
[grunts]
[Kyo] Dude.
[Taiki] I have to,
it's the only chance I have
of getting on her level.
[pants]
You are aware
that you've got a slim chance of making it
to nationals in your first year?
Given your current skills,
it may be impossible--
Maybe you're right, maybe not...
But it won't stop me from trying!
[sighs]
So come on, play me again!
Resting is a key part of training.
What?
- [Nishida] Taiki! I'll take you on!
- [Taiki] All right!
Huh? He's playing someone else now?
Hasn't he been playing the whole practice?
Once he sets his mind on something,
there's no stopping him.
What's he set on?
Apparently, he wants to go
to nationals this year.
And...
Do you think he can?
- Uh...
- [chuckles]
It's just, he always pushes himself.
[giggles]
[Kyo] Well, at the end of the day,
those who go after what they want
are usually the strongest...
in everything they do.
- [clattering]
- [Taiki] Forty-five.
Forty-six.
Forty-seven.
WORKOUT ROUTINE
Forty-eight. Forty-nine.
[straining] Fifty!
[grunting]
[Taiki] I'm beat.
But... I gotta keep at it.
Playing like this
won't get me to nationals.
A dream will stay a dream
if you don't wake up, Taiki!
[Chinatsu] Uh...
[Taiki] Chinatsu!
What are you watching?
Oh, you know, just... something dumb!
I had someone film me playing,
so I was watching it to see my form.
- Show me!
- What?
- No way. It's too embarrassing!
- Oh, come on.
I watch you practice all the time anyway.
[Taiki] And here I thought
I was the only one watching.
[mellow music playing]
Wow, you're so good.
Being able to react to a birdie that fast,
and flying around the court like that...
No way. I still move too slow.
My first step needs to be faster,
or my shots won't be as accurate.
I'm barely keeping up.
I need to be collected
to make those shots.
I'll never get
to nationals like this. [gasps]
Wait nationals?
Err. No, I meant like, uh...
I had decided I wouldn't tell her...
until it felt like
I had a shot at making it.
- You said it.
- Huh?
So you're going to nationals,
then, huh, Taiki?
Huh? I meant something else.
What, you're not going?
Even though you just said it out loud?
[breathing heavily] Please, Chinatsu.
You have... to go to nationals.
[grunts] I'll go. I'm going to nationals!
Ah, man.
Why do I always come off
as such a doofus around her?
Hold on just a sec.
[mellow music ends]
Take this, if you want.
[Taiki] A wish bracelet?
I made this one
when I decided to stay in Japan.
As a wish, I guess.
I was hoping it would
help me feel more courageous.
If you don't like it, that's o--
I am honored!
She gave me something!
And she made it with her own two hands!
I will treasure it till the end of time.
[Chinatsu] You'll cut off
the blood flow like that.
[gasps softly]
[romantic music playing]
Taiki...
you have to...
go to nationals.
Ta-da.
Look.
We match.
Don't be too careful with it.
Night!
Good night, Chinatsu.
Let's do this.
I'll work till this falls off.
That's the thought, but...
[groans]
This only...
makes me like her even more.
Every time I start daydreaming about her,
I'll do 30 sit-ups.
[birds chirping]
Oh. You're leaving already?
It's spring break,
and you're still going early?
I'm a newbie,
so I get the set up grunt work.
Plus, I need to practice, too.
Have a good day!
You... have a day, too.
It felt like we were married for a second.
What are you doing?
Keeping distractions at bay! [grunts]
[Hina] Distractions?
The preliminaries are coming up soon.
I gotta stay focused.
Don't tell me, something went down
between you and basketball girl.
[exclaims]
- [groans]
- Is that it?
[cheerful music playing]
So what happened?
Nothing.
Did you get into her phone or something?
I'm not a stalker.
This is bad.
If Hina figures out we live together,
it'll be all kinds of trouble.
What a development in your love story!
Let me tell you, this is a grand tale,
the story of one man's quest for love.
He played badminton, and she...
- [boy 1] Is that him?
- [boy 2] Yeah, that's the guy.
[Taiki] I have to keep this
under wraps no matter what.
- You left your wallet at home.
- [screams]
I thought I dropped it somewhere!
Thank you very much
for returning it to me!
- [Chinatsu] Uh...
- [grunts nervously]
You're welcome, happy to help.
[Taiki] Was I a bit...
rude just now?
[Hina] Wow, you can talk to her now?
You've come so far.
[Taiki] This twerp.
That kind of thing
is just not a strong point for you.
You should've just told her you wanted
to keep living together a secret.
That is the least of my worries.
This is bad, right?
Is it bad to, I don't know,
have someone avoid you out of nowhere?
You wanting to keep it a secret
may've made her think
you don't like living with her.
Or worse,
she could be wondering if you don't want
anything to do with her at all.
[Taiki] It's actually
the complete opposite!
PRIVILEGE OF GETTING TO SEE
SENPAI'S SLEEPY SIDE
Both of you!
What is it, sir?
Help me carry these, would you?
They're for next week's entrance ceremony.
[Taiki] We'll be taking part, actually.
[teacher] No, I need you to take them all.
- [Taiki] He's not listening.
- I need you two to help as well.
[Hina exclaims]
[teacher] Okay, athletes.
I'm counting on you.
[Kyo grunts]
[Taiki] I need to straighten
this out with her ASAP.
I don't want her
to take this the wrong way,
and think I want nothing to do with her.
Um... I can carry one of those for you.
I'm good.
[Taiki] Oh god, she is even angrier
than I had feared!
- [Chinatsu] Is the main entrance okay?
- Yep.
[Taiki] It's fine, she probably picked up
on needing to act like a stranger.
She's not gonna hate me
because of what happened earlier, right?
Why are you enjoying this?
[playful music playing]
Um, you're Chinatsu, right?
Yeah.
- Do you mind if I ask you a question?
- No.
Do you have someone special
in your life, like a boyfriend?
- [Taiki] You idiot!
- No, no boyfriend.
How can she act so casual
about something like that?
That's not a question
you ask an upperclassman.
- Look, dude. She's a gymnast.
- What does that even mean!
But wait, wouldn't you like a boyfriend?
You can walk home together.
Go out together.
Right now,
I'm pretty focused on basketball.
[Hina trembling nervously]
[Taiki] You asked the question.
Stop looking so uncomfortable.
[playful music ends]
And anyway...
I knew that was going to be her answer.
Oh! You're club members, right?
Look at you here on spring break.
Yeah, we got recruited
to help out with errands today!
What an impressive group.
Oh, Inomata.
Coach Yuasa was singing your praises.
He said your shots have developed
a lot of power recently.
Wait, he said that?
Yeah!
He said you're looking good
to play at the high school level.
And that you have a good shot at making
the team for the next national qualifiers.
[exclaims] Did you hear that, Chinatsu?
She's quick to head back.
[Hina whispers] Hey, really,
did something happen between those two?
She's giving him the cold shoulder.
I was just thinking
that they suit each other better
than I thought.
[exclaims]
[rackets whooshing]
[grunts]
He's really going for it.
High school is
just around the corner for him.
Thank you for the match!
I don't know.
I thought about it,
and I'm starting to feel annoyed.
I wish...
I could talk about it.
- Maybe even go around bragging about it.
- [thuds]
Huh?
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah.
I can tell you're worried.
But you can't go check on her, right?
You're just strangers to one another.
Well, that's just mean.
[footsteps approaching]
[Taiki] Are you okay?
[exclaims softly]
Because I saw you fall earlier.
Yes, I'm all right, but...
aren't you supposed to be pretending
that you and I don't know each other?
[Taiki] I'm sorry about that.
Acting like that out of the blue.
I guess I still feel a little awkward
about living together.
And people pay attention to you
more than you realize.
If word got out,
people would make up crazy stories.
I worried you wouldn't be able
to focus on your club.
- That's why I did it.
- What?
That was the reason?
What other reason would I have?
A-ha.
I figured...
that it was because
you have a crush on the girl
who's on the rhythmic gymnastics team.
What?
When you started acting
like you didn't know me, she was there.
[Taiki] That was...
[Chinatsu] I thought
the reason she asked me
if I had a boyfriend
was because she liked you,
and so she was trying to see how I felt.
I'd understand wanting to hide us
living together from someone you liked.
I was going to just keep away from you,
so no one would catch on.
If it comes to it,
I can sleep in the shed.
Or I could probably find
a cheap apartment somewhere.
[Taiki] So everything up to now...
is 'cause she was looking out
for me and Hina?
Oh man. She's adorable.
[laughs] That's stupid, Chinatsu.
[exclaims]
[peaceful music playing]
[grunts softly]
[laughing]
Hey, quit laughing.
[Taiki] I can't help it.
[Chinatsu] Whatever.
[Taiki] No, I'm sorry.
[peaceful music ends]
[birds chirping]
[Coach Yuasa] Everyone, congratulations
on entering your next year.
While it may be a busy time of year,
the national qualifiers
are just around the corner.
You'll all face off in matches together.
That'll determine who goes to qualifiers.
[all] Yes, sir!
We've got a long road ahead
to get to nationals.
First, get selected for the club's lineup,
then get in the top 16 for regionals.
After that, the top two
for prefectural qualifiers.
[Kyo] We have to at least beat Haryu,
who was third in the prefecture last time.
[Taiki] If you reframe it,
beating Haryu means we have
a chance at getting to nationals.
That is a pretty clear goal.
What are your stats up to now, by the way?
Don't ask that!
We have a larger crowd than usual.
[Kyo] I bet a lot of them
are new to the school and observing.
But, I think most of them
are probably here to watch.
[all] Whoa!
- Her fan base keeps growing every year.
- [grunts]
And anyone who's not here
for her, is here to watch...
[whimsical music playing]
[all gasp]
Just fantastic!
Miss Chono!
So wonderful. Beautiful. Fantastic!
The star of the club!
The one the gymnastic goddesses
smiled upon!
You and me...
Let's make us number one in Japan!
There's high hopes for that girl.
[girl 1] I'm a senior,
but I feel like a nobody now.
[girl 2] Wasn't she 4th in juniors?
Her father was on the national team
for gymnastics, too, is what I heard.
[girl 1] She really does seem
like the chosen one.
It's 2,000 yen to watch me.
I'm not paying that!
I don't know, you were giving me
some intense looks.
[Taiki] I wasn't giving you anything!
I completely understand
that beautiful things
are hard to look away from.
[Taiki] Don't be so full of yourself!
Why are you the way that you are!
The gymnastics club is so cool.
Yeah.
Right, then!
Back to practicing!
Mm.
[Taiki] This isn't good.
She keeps seeing me with Hina like that.
No wonder she has the wrong idea.
[giggles] Made ya look!
Hina! Why are you here?
Your house is the other way, right?
Actually, there's a new clinic
in Azuma-cho,
it's run by a famous chiropractor, apparently.
I know it. My house is near...
[gasps] Hold on, uh-oh.
If Hina sees Chinatsu,
going into the Inomata household...
[mischievous music playing]
Chinatsu should still be at school.
I need to get Hina outta here, fast.
Let's get you there before it's busy.
Okay then.
- [Hina exclaims]
- Hm?
- What a little cutie.
- Hey!
You look just like Uncle Shuhei.
[Taiki] Stop saying things
no one understands but you!
- [dog pants]
- [Hina] Bye-bye.
[Taiki] She's the youngest child
and has type B blood. Typical.
PREJUDICED
Then again,
Hina doesn't understand the situation.
Oh, so good!
[Taiki] She's doing it on purpose.
Look, they have bean paste!
TAIYAKI
Okay, okay, I'll buy you one,
and then let's get going.
[Hina] Huh?
I'm good.
Hina...
Your face says otherwise.
No, but...
my daily calorie limit.
I'll go over.
It's all that sugar.
If one has even just 40 grams, then...
Is that how you think
about things every day?
Of course.
Putting on just a few hundred grams...
that can make me move slower.
Then training in order to lose
that weight, it's a waste of time.
And I don't want
to get injured or hit a slump.
Working hard isn't something
that I'm good at.
If I can just grin and bear it,
then I'll do that.
What's with your face?
It's just...
I was thinking that you're pretty cool.
Well, that isn't what it looked like.
[Taiki] The fact that you can resist
taiyaki in the first place is impressive.
[mellow music playing]
But then you don't even see it as effort?
It shows how disciplined you are
throughout your life.
When I look at what "normal" is,
what my normal is compared to the normal
of athletes much better than me,
it makes me nervous.
And then I see you
going for it alongside them.
It makes me think
that you're so freaking cool!
What is this?
What's with all the feelings?
Quit it! Don't act so chill after that!
I'll never say it to you again.
[Hina] But Mr. Taiki, I think
you're actually the cooler one.
Finding the courage to talk to a girl
who's totally out of your league!
[Taiki] You're making fun of me!
If there is any assistance I can
provide you, my lord, say the word.
I'll do it!
Drop that character for starters.
Even if you could help me
with this whole thing,
there's nothing in it for you.
Well, that may be true.
But good sir, we should return
to the former topic of discussion!
[Taiki] I'm not a "sir."
Your courage
in surmounting this challenge,
I think it's pretty cool, my lord!
Whoosh!
As your best friend,
I want you to taste victory.
Hina, why are you being so theatrical
- all of a sudden?
- Huh?
- Wait, what's going on?
- No, don't look!
[exclaims]
[Taiki] It's Chinatsu and...
Haryu?
[closing theme song playing]